Most cars run on fuel. This one runs on blood.
Super Hybrid is a horror film directed by Eric Valette.
Late one night, a mysterious car is brought into the Chicago
police impound garage after a deadly traffic accident.
The on-call mechanics soon discover the car has a mind of its own.
With hundreds of horsepower and two tons of reinforced steel at its command, it's a seemingly
unstoppable killing machine capable of outrunning -- and outwitting -- humans.
Tilda, played by Shannon Beckner.
Ray, played by Oded Fehr.
Bobby, played by Ryan Kennedy.
Gordy, played by Adrien Dorval.
Maria, played by Melanie Papalia.
David, played by John Reardon.
Super Hybrid is a 2011 science fiction horror thriller film directed by Eric Valette and
starring Shannon Beckner, Oded Fehr, Ryan Kennedy, and Melanie Papalia.
The screenplay follows a malicious shape shifting sentient car that devours its victims by tricking them into its cab, and then sent
to a police precinct garage after a terrible accident, and stalks the mechanics as it tries to find a way to escape.
The tone is dark.